<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on Borko D.</title>
    <link>https://borkod.github.io/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on Borko D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 14:00:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://borkod.github.io/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ignite the Tour: Toronto Recap</title>
      <link>https://borkod.github.io/2020/01/microsoft-ignite-the-tour-toronto-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 14:00:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borkod.github.io/2020/01/microsoft-ignite-the-tour-toronto-recap/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Ignite the Tour conference is a two-day version of Microsoft&#39;s annual Ignite technology conference that Microsoft is bringing to a number of cities around the world. Last week I had the opportunity to attend the conference in Toronto. As usual at these types of events, there was &amp;ldquo;The Hub&amp;rdquo;, a central meeting place where large number of sponsors had booths set up demonstrating their products or services and giving out SWAG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Database - Specialty Exam Preparation Guide and Study Tips</title>
      <link>https://borkod.github.io/2020/01/aws-certified-database-specialty-exam-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 23:09:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borkod.github.io/2020/01/aws-certified-database-specialty-exam-guide/</guid>
      <description>In late November of 2019, AWS announced a new specialty certification focusing specifically on database technologies. The AWS Certified Database - Specialty Exam beta period started in early December of 2019 with the standard certification exam availability target date being April of 2020. At the start of December, I participated in the beta attempting the beta exams. As of this writing, I do not know my results and whether on not I achieved the certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://borkod.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borkod.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Cloud Solutions Architect with the goal of helping people take advantage of cloud technologies provided by Azure and AWS. I have huge interests in learning, technology and science. You can learn more about me here.
This blog is a place I occasionally try to write some thoughts on Cloud computing and related topics. I hope others find them useful, insightful, or just interesting.
The blog is hosted using Github Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
